<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Vim | Modern Web Development | Ruby on Rails | React | Vim]]></title>
  <link href="http://loganrice.github.io/loganrice/blog/categories/vim/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://loganrice.github.io/loganrice/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-07T14:27:32-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://loganrice.github.io/loganrice/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Logan Rice]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Switching From Sublime Text to Vim]]></title>
    <link href="http://loganrice.github.io/loganrice/blog/2015/04/07/switching-from-sublime-text-to-vim/"/>
    <updated>2015-04-07T12:35:02-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://loganrice.github.io/loganrice/blog/2015/04/07/switching-from-sublime-text-to-vim</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As programmers we value or tools and workflows. We strive to be efficient and automate repititive tasks. We also, come to know our text editing software very well. When it comes to writing code I always thought my typing and navigation skills were acceptible. That was until, I watched someone use vim. If you have ever witnessed an experienced vim user write code, then you know what I am talking about. And if you don&rsquo;t know about Vim you should check it out. Watching an experienced Vim user is like watching someone program at the speed of thought.</p>

<p>My current text editor is Sublime Text; which I have come to love. There are lots of things you can do with Sublime. If offers plugins, custom configurations, and lots of command shortcuts. Sublime even offers a Vim mode, which can allow you to navigate using keyboard commands.</p>

<p>I have been dabbling with Vim for a few weeks now and using Vim mode primarily inside Sublime Text. Now I am planning on making the switch to Vim 100%. It&rsquo;s going to be painful. Learning Vim is going to be a journey. For me, going all in is the only way I am going to learn. I will write a few more posts about my expierence and share some my .vimrc file along the way.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
